Town Council Minutes and Ordinance Books for the City of Lexington, Virginia WLU.Coll.0698
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Town Council Minutes and Ordinance Books for the City of Lexington, Virginia
Inclusive August 1835-August 1958
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
WLU.Coll.0698
14 Item
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of 12 folio sized leather bound minute books documenting the meetings of the Lexington, Virginia Town Council, from August 1835 to August 1958 accompanied by two folio sized leather bound ordinance books from the Lexington Town Council. The first volume of town ordinances dates from August 1874 to August 1903 and the second volume dates from Februay 1911 to December 1931.
Municipal government; Virginia -- Lexington; Corporate minutes
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 1, 1835-08-1860-01
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 2, 1860-01-1873-08
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 3, 1873-09-1881-01
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 4, 1881-02-1890-07
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 5, 1890-07-1900-09
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 6, 1900-10-1903-08
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 7, 1903-09-1910-02
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 8, 1910-02-1913-04
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 9, 1913-05-1921-06
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 10, 1921-07-1933-08
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 11, 1933-09-1946-11
- Lexington Town Council Minutes Book 12, 1946-11-1958-08
- Lexington Town Council Ordinance Book 1, 1874-08-1903-08
- Lexington Town Council Ordinance Book 2, 1911-02-1931-12